University Railroad Collection 1997.0041
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series V: Gift of Carl Leaman, 1858-1919 (Box 28, Folder 107)
  - Timetables, New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, 1879-1919
    - New York & New Haven Division (Boston and the East), 1879 May 12
    - Boston and the East, 1879 November 5
    - New York Division, 1882 May 1
    - Shore Line Route to New York and all points south and west, 1894 September 22
    - New York & New Haven Division (Western district), 1898 December 4
    - New York & New Haven Division (East of New London and Willimantic), 1902 July 12
    - New York & New Haven Division (Lines West of New London and Willimantic), 1903 May 3
    - East of New London and Willimantic, 1904 May 29
    - Providence Division, Suburban Service, 1904 October 30
    - East of New London and Willimantic, 1905 June 11
    - New York and Boston, All Rail Lines, 1906 June 10
    - Local time-table between Boston and eastern Connecticut, 1908 June 15
    - Lines West of New London and Willimantic, 1910 April 4
    - East of New London and Willimantic, 1910 April 4
    - Winter schedule, Lines West of New London and Willimantic (2 copies), 1911 October 1
    - Winter schedule, Lines East of New London and Willimantic, 1911 October 1
    - New England, the Maritime Provinces, Montreal and Quebec, 1915 June 27
    - Lines East of New London and Willimantic, 1916 July 23
    - Lines West of New London and Willimantic, 1918 August 19
    - New York, Stamford, S. Norwalk, Bridgeport, New Haven (note: timetable indicates that the railroad was being operated by the U.S. Railroad Administration), 1918 October 31
    - New York, Stamford, S. Norwalk, Bridgeport, New Haven (note: timetable indicates that the railroad was being operated by the U.S. Railroad Administration), 1919 January 26
    - New York, Stamford, S. Norwalk, Bridgeport, New Haven (note: timetable indicates that the railroad was being operated by the U.S. Railroad Administration), 1919 June 8
    - Lines East of New London and Willimantic, 1919 December 8
  - Timetable, Hartford, Providence & Fishkill Railroad, 1874
  - Timetable, New York, Providence & Boston Railroad, 1874 June 22
  - Timetables, Connecticut Valley Railroad, 1873-1874
    - 1873 June 9
    - (3"x5" card), 1874 November 30
  - Poster, Lowell and Lawrence Railroad Fall Arrangements, On & after Monday, November 1, 1858 (2 copies)
  - Timetables, Old Colony Railroad, 1879-1888
    - Northern Division, 1879 June 30
    - Northern Division, 1884 June 30
    - Fall River Line, 1888 September 30
  - General Rules for Lowell & Lawrence and Salem & Lowell Railroads, with Time-Tables and Ruse of Gorham Smith, 1862
  - Other items, 1910-1944
    - Electric Lines of the New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, Their Operation in Connecticut and Rhode Island. Reprinted from the Boston Evening Transcript, by Baxter Sylvester, 1910 June 4 and 15
    - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, Station numbers which must be used in making our Conductors' Passenger Train Reports..., 1944 October 15